[
  { "question": "What is the Wi-Fi password in the library", "options": ["12345678", "ilovebooks", "library@123", "nointernet"], "answer": "library@123" },
  { "question": "What is the color of the walls in Lab-5?", "options": ["Blue", "White", "Black", "Transparent"], "answer": "White" },
  { "question": "How many fans are there in Classroom R3/R4?", "options": ["2", "4", "10", "0"], "answer": "4" },
  { "question": "What is the most famous snack in the canteen?", "options": ["Samosa", "Sushi", "Whopper", "Caviar"], "answer": "Samosa" },
  { "question": "Which teacher always asks 'Did you understand?' after every line?", "options": ["Sharma Sir", "Gupta Maâ€™am", "Patel Sir", "Verma Sir"], "answer": "Verma Sir" },
  { "question": "What is written on the notice board near the canteen?", "options": ["Exam Timetable", "Free Wi-Fi Zone", "No Smoking, Only Dancing", "Today's Menu: Pizza"], "answer": "Exam Timetable" },
  { "question": "Which lab has the broken chair everyone avoids?", "options": ["Lab 1", "Lab 3", "Lab 5", "Lab 7"], "answer": "Lab 3" },
  { "question": "How many steps are there on the staircase (Library side) from ground to first floor?", "options": ["25", "30", "50", "I stopped counting"], "answer": "30" },
  
  { "question": "Which computer in Lab 2 never works?", "options": ["PC1", "PC4", "PC7", "PC13"], "answer": "PC7" },

  { "question": "Which subject class has the maximum bunk rate?", "options": ["Deep Learning", "Linux Lab", "Compiler Design", "COA"], "answer": "Linux Lab" },
  { "question": "What sound does the projector make before starting?", "options": ["Beep", "Buzz", "Explosion-like", "Silent"], "answer": "Buzz" },
  { "question": "Which water cooler gives water that tastes like tea?", "options": ["Ground Floor", "First Floor", "Second Floor", "Rooftop"], "answer": "First Floor" },
   { "question": "What color is the ceiling fan in the seminar hall?", "options": ["White", "Rust Brown", "Golden", "Invisibility"], "answer": "Rust Brown" },
   { "question": "Which lift always gets stuck between floors?", "options": ["Lift A", "Lift B", "Lift C", "Imaginary Lift"], "answer": "Imaginary Lift" },
   { "question": "What animal once entered the classroom during a lecture?", "options": ["Cat", "Dog", "Monkey", "Cow"], "answer": "Dog" }
]
